killerdana.com 2010-06-23

# FAQ & Privacy Policy at Killer Dana Surf Shop - Home of the Boardshort Superstore

## How can I check on my order?

We offer a feature to check the status of your order on our site [Click here to access your order history](http://www.killerdana.info/emordersummary.aspx). You may also call one of our amazing customer service representatives at 1.800.228.7873. They are waiting for your call from 9-5 p.m. PST.

## I have received my confirmation email but what is my order status?

Our system sends any person ordering from Killer Dana an initial confirmation email. This email will contain the complete order details only. The tracking and shipment details will come in a later email once the package has been processed.

## How do I return an item/order to Killer Dana?

All returns must be accompanied by our [Return Form](http://www.killerdana.com/killerdana/assets/images/ra_form.pdf). Fill it out completely and legibly using blue or black ink. Items must be returned within 30 days – no returns are accepted after 30 days from purchase date. Product must be in new, unused condition (no pet hair, odors, signs of wear, etc.) with tags in place. Once we receive your return, it can take up to 3 weeks to process your return and credit your account. Your credit card company may require up to an additional 5–7 days to post the credit to your account. Repackage your return item(s) in the original packaging and return the parcel along with this mandatory [Return Form](http://www.killerdana.com/killerdana/assets/images/ra_form.pdf).

**Send to:**  
Killer Dana  
**ATTN: Returns Dept.**  
14370 Myford Rd  
Suite 150  
Irvine CA 92606

## What about return shipping & handling?

Killer Dana uses SmartLabel, a simple and convenient return solution offered to our customers. If applicable, attach the pre-paid, pre-addressed return label on the other side of the packing slip to your return package. You pay nothing up front. We will deduct a $7.95 shipping cost from your refund. There is no charge for product mistakes on our behalf. Just leave the package with your mail carrier or drop it off at any U.S. Mail location. To track, go to [**http://tracking.smartlabel.com/**](http://tracking.smartlabel.com/) and use the SmartLabel tracking number found on the front of the packing slip. Please retain the top portion of your packing slip for your records.

**Please follow these steps:**

  1. Select the items you are returning, including a reason code in the shaded section.

  2. Indicate if you would like a refund or to order an alternate item (use the appropriate reason code).

  3. Enclose the return form in the original package (perforate at center section) retain the upper portion for your records.

  4. Remove or cover any other labels and barcodes from the package.

_Unfortunately we are unable to offer SmartLabel® returns for packages shipped to Alaska, Hawaii, U.S. Territories, APO/FPO addresses or other countries._

If you ship a return package on your own, please make sure to use a traceable **and** insured shipping method and send to the address below:

> **Killer Dana Returns**  
>  **14370 Myford Rd**  
>  **Suite 150**  
>  **Irvine, CA 92606**  
>  **SO#WEB____________**

## What is considered returnable merchandise?

We will accept the return of new, unworn, and tag still attached product. This means no human or pet hair allowed on the merchandise. Items that come to us smelling of smoke, cologne, or detergent will not be accepted. Pretty much anything that doesn’t smell new. Footwear must not be worn and have the original packaging (if any) and have all tags still attached. Surfboards cannot be returned without prior approval. Skateboards and skate accessories that are not ridden and are in the original packaging are accepted.

## What if I received a defective/incorrect product?

_Defective Merchandise_ : Killer Dana cannot guarantee the return for a defective item. This is because the item might no longer be in stock or that the item might look defective. What we mean is that some vendors make worn out looking items for that style or look. If the item is believed to be defective please return the item explaining the reason in the return portion of the receipt. 

_Incorrect items_ : Unfortunately, these mistakes do happen from time to time. We try our best to avoid them in shipping but once in a while they slip past us. If for any reason that you receive the incorrect merchandise, please return your incorrect item with the filled out return receipt, please see returns section for further detail. We will ship out the correct item with free ground shipping. No express shipping reimbursement will be permitted.

## My surfboard is damaged!

Please trust us that we would NEVER send a damaged surfboard (or any other goods for that matter). If this does occur please **SAVE ALL** packaging and contact us immediately at (800) 228-7873 and email us at info@killerdana.com. There is a process that the shipping carrier is going to need to perform to help process all claims.

  * If the damage is less than $100 we will gladly pay for the ding repair.

  * If the damage is greater than $100 we will have the board shipped back to us.

## What happens if something I order is out of stock?

Thanks to amazing technology and trial and error we have implemented a system to remove out-of-stock items from the online store. However, nobody is perfect. Contact our customer service department and we’ll do our best to help out when this situation occurs.

## How long does it take to process my return and/or credit?

Once returns are received we process them as soon as possible. However, certain times of the year take longer than expected. Usually, we have returns fully processed within approximately 3 weeks, this includes credits. Your issuing bank may take an additional billing cycle to display the credit to your card.

## Is my return guaranteed?

Killer Dana cannot guarantee any returns that are not received when shipped using a service other than the SmartLabel. To prevent this type of situation please make sure to use a traceable and insured shipping method. When returns are received, assuming the item(s) are in new/unused condition (see above requirements) your returns will be processed promptly.

## When will I know that my order has shipped?

The second email that is sent by our site will be the shipment confirmation email. This email will give you all that you need to track your package. This email will also include the date of shipment and the expected delivery date.

## What companies do you use for shipping?

We use Federal Express (FedEx) and USPS. Within FedEx there is also our “economy” shipping method, called SmartPost. This works by FedEx processing all of the package sorting and then delivers the package to your nearest USPS center. Once the package arrives at the USPS center your postman becomes the deliverer. Yes, SmartPost does take longer than other methods, but it offers our customers an economically friendly shipping price and great service. 

## What if I’m a foreign customer?

We are stoked that so many people outside of the United States want to be a part of Killer Dana’s surf culture. We do our best to handle these orders, but you should be aware of the following:

  * **Foreign customers are responsible for any and all fees and taxes that are incurred**. You can obtain more information at your local customs office. All goods are shipped FOB our warehouse. This means: 

_FOB- An International Term of Sale that means the seller fulfills his or her obligation to deliver when the goods have passed over the border at the named border of the country. This means that the buyer has to bear all costs and risks to loss of or damage to the goods from that point. ** _This includes the duties and taxes_**. The FOB term requires the seller to clear the goods for export._

  * The “Ship To” and “Bill To” addresses must be the same on all foreign addresses. ****

  * Large items, such as surfboards, board bags, beach chairs, etc. are not available for shipment outside of the U.S. and Canada. ****

  * Process time on these orders can take up to 4 business days. ****

  * **Surfboards** cannot be shipped outside of the U.S. ****

## What countries does Killer Dana ship to?

To look at the countries that we have cleared for shipping please follow this link. **[Country List](http://www.killerdana.com/Killer%20Dana/Country%20List.mht)**. 

## When will I know that my order has shipped?

The second email that is sent by our site will be the shipment confirmation email. This email will give you all that you need to track your package. This email will also include the date of shipment and the expected delivery date.

## How long does it take Killerdana to ship my order?

At Killerdana, we strive to ship your order within 24-72 hours (business days Mon-Fri) of receiving it, **excluding weekends and holidays**. We don't ship on weekends and are unable to ship on holidays. You will receive an email notifying you when your order ships including a tracking/confirmation number. During peak periods - such as Christmas - we may need an extra day or three to ship your package. We ship with Federal Express, Federal Express SmartPost, and USPS. Which carrier we choose depends on what type of shipping you choose (economy, priority ground, express, international, or APO/FPO,). While we try to give orders with Express Shipping special attention, orders placed after 11:00 a.m. EST/08:00 a.m. PST usually do not go out until the next shipping day (so if you order Friday afternoon, your package won't ship until Monday). At Christmas, Priority Mail may take in excess of 7 days to reach you. Certain products - namely board bags, boards, beach chairs, and other heavy or large items may take longer (usually 7-10 days). These items are **NOT** available for Express delivery. If you need something extra fast, please give us a call at 1.800.228.7873 and we will try our best to accommodate you. Orders for Alaska and Hawaii are shipped via USPS and Federal Express, so please make sure that you provide a deliverable shipping address. See shipping table below for more information.  

## How long does it take to receive my surfboard?

Thanks to FedEx and various other shipping couriers we have seen delivery only take up to 7 business days from the point of shipment. Surfboards need extra care for proper shipment and we would like to have 2 business days to process the order.  

## What is incremental charging?

Because we are often not capable of gaining the credit card address verification information on foreign addresses, we may require additional information before we can process your order.

We have begun using a process called “Incremental Charging.”  The way that this works is we will gain your consent to place two small charges on your account. These charges will range from$0.01 to $1.00 USD. Then we will require that you please email us with the proper amounts that were charged to your account. Once this is verified we will continually ship to you as a customer **under the card that the incremental charges were placed** , if a new card is to be used we will need to verify that card as well. This method is securing all of the hard working people and Killer Dana from potential fraud orders because we can not always verify the credit card information. This is not to push away customers but a security for all since there are always people trying to steal and harm the hard workers.

| 

## Shipping

| 

**Your Order Total**

| 

**USA Economy  
(7-14 Business Days)**

| 

**USA Priority Ground  
(3-5 Business Days)**

| 

**Express**  
**(1-2  Business Day)**

| 

**Canada  
(2-4 Business Days)**

| 

**International  
(7-10 Business Days)**  
  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**$0-$59.99**

| 

**$5.00**

| 

**$8.50**

| 

**$15.00**

| 

**$32.00**

| 

**$30.00**  
  
**$60-$99.99**

| 

**$5.00**

| 

**$11.50**

| 

**$25.00**

| 

**$37.00**

| 

**$50.00**  
  
**$100 +**

| 

**$5.00**

| 

**$14.00**

| 

**$30.00**

| 

**$42.00**

| 

**$70.00**  
  
## Surfboard Shipping

| 

**Board Size**

| 

**Shipping Cost**

| 

**Shipping Method**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**All Boards 7'0"  
and UNDER **

| 

**$49.99**

| 

**Ground Shipping** (7-14 Business Days)  
  
**All Boards 7'1"  
and OVER***

| 

**$149.99 +**

| 

**Ground Shipping** (7-14 Business Days) **  
*For Longboards its best to email our Surfboard Buyer for accurate shipping rates. Email:[KD Board Buyer ](mailto:%20traut@killerdana.com)**  
  
_*****Estimated transit time to military addresses (APO and FPO), Alaska, and Hawaii is between 14-45 days going Economy**._

  * Foreign customers are responsible for all brokerage fees and taxes incurred during shipping. Goods are shipped FOB our warehouse.

  * Oversize items such as boards, board bags, and anything larger than a bunch of clothes are **NOT** available for express shipping.

  * Oversize items such as boards and board bags carry an oversize shipping charge. 

  * APO/FPO orders will be traveling via USPS; unfortunately there is no delivery confirmation or express shipping for these orders.

  * Alaska/Hawaii/Puerto Rico are shipped the Priority Ground method, Express consists of 2nd Day express, and please make sure that you provide a deliverable address. 

  * Most in stock orders are shipped within 72 hours (3 business days) **excluding weekends and holidays**

  * Economy method orders are sent with delivery confirmation; these packages do not have exact tracking. 

  * Orders may be shipped via Fed Ex, Fed Ex Smart Post, or USPS at our discretion. 

  * "Bill to" customer may be contacted on all orders over $200.00. 

  * "Bill to" customer may be contacted on all orders with a different ship to address. 

## Do you ship surfboards?

Killer Dana not only has taken over the boardshort market and now has its eye set on surfboards. Our goal is to try to maintain at the very minimum 1,000 surfboards constantly. From vintage to the latest fad, Killer Dana will carry it for you and keep you shredding.

## Where do you ship surfboards?

Killer Dana can only ship to the continental United States. No PO Box shipments allowed. **_The person ordering the surfboard must be available to sign for the board at the time of delivery._**

## I'm having trouble with my shopping cart.

Due to the way we upload and process our inventory data, we may experience a shopping cart "clearing" once a day. This usually happens in the middle of the night and only takes a minute. However, if you lose the items in your cart during checkout please either: call us so we can complete your order or just recreate the cart. If you get a timeout error or any other error when trying to complete an order, please call us at 1.800.228.7873 and we will take your order over the phone. You browser does need to allow cookies in order for items to be placed into your cart.

## How do I navigate in Killerdana.com?

The latest version of our website has a really cool feature called "guided navigation." This lets you drill down into the products by category, brand, gender, size, color, and price. This way, you can see exactly the stuff that you are interested in. Overwhelmed by 800 styles of boardshorts, start by just getting those together that are available in your size. With this new feature, you may start with more choices than you are used to, but you can quickly get into a group that is exactly what you like. You can even select a vendor from the menu and then type in a search term - our site will actually look at both these entries at the same time and bring back an exact group. Need to go back? We now have a cookie crumble on the page that shows the path you took to get where you are. Click any of the items in the crumble to go back there.

## I can't find the items I want.

If you are overwhelmed by the myriad of choices in our site, or if you can't find the item you desire, give us a call at 1.800.228.7873 so that we can try to find it for you. You can also email us at [info@killerdana.com.](mailto:info@killerdana.com)

## Why are there so many boardshorts? Why?

The reason behind this theory of ours is to offer you almost every style from many different brands. Normally you do not get to come even close to seeing the entire universe of boardshorts at your local shops or online. We at Killer Dana want to make that a possibility for you. For some brands, we have almost every style and typically in many different color ways. This can lead us to having hundreds of styles, but who cares. We simply love boardshorts. We have created the [Boardshort Superstore](http://www.killerdana.com/killerdana/search2.asp?search_submitted=yes&move=none&prod_sort=0&q_count=1&q0typ=cat&q0val1=93&q0val2=boardshorts&seach_freetext=&) as an entry point for you surf trunk adventure. There is even a [Boardshort Buyer's Guide](http://www.killerdana.com/killerdana/dept.asp?s_id=0&dept_id=11005) to help you understand your many choices.

## Can I become a Killer Dana affiliate?

Join many of the surfing world's best known companies and become a Killer Dana Affiliate. If you have a website that is dedicated to surfing, we'd be stoked to team up with you. Killer Dana is the leading surf specific online retailer selling all the best brands and highest quality products. If your website's visitors are looking for these types of products, we are the obvious company with whom to team up. Commission Junction runs our affiliate program.  You can find our links and information there.  Visit for more information and to sign up.

## What is the Killer Dana Rewards Program?

Anyone who shops at Killer Dana or www.killerdana.com is eligible to earn KD Rewards Points. Basically, we give you 10% of the value of your purchases back in points. Customers get 10 points per dollar spent on regular priced items and 5 points per dollar spent on sale priced items. Spend $100 on regularly priced items at Killer Dana, and you will get 1000 points. You can then spend those points on the KD Rewards site a www.kdrewards.com. You must have enough points to cover your full purchase - you cannot use part points and part credit card. Points can also only be redeemed online. They cannot be used in-store. Points expire 2 years after being earned. Anyone who provides Killer†Dana with an email address is eligible for KD Rewards Points.

## Does Killer Dana offer rentals and lessons?

We have a full fleet of soft surfboards from 7'0" to 11'0" for every surfer. We now even have stand up paddle boards for rent. We also have wetsuits, bodyboards, and any accessories you might need for surfing all for rent at great daily rates. We also have a staff of trained instructors ready to give you your first taste of surfing or help you take your skills to the next level. We also can put together a group package anywhere from 2 to 100 people. We are experienced in doing group lessons for special groups and events. Please call our Dana Point store, 1.949.489.8380, for more information on lessons.

## Where are your stores located?

We have now grown to having two locations. A big accomplishment for us and we would love to have you visit them both. Here are the locations and directions for you to come and visit us.  [ Home of the Boardshort Superstores](http://www.killerdana.com/killerdana/dept.asp?s_id=0&dept_id=3325)  

##  **Killer Dana - Dana Point**  
24621 Del Prado,   
Dana Point, CA 92629, USA  
(949) 489.8380 

**Dana Point Store Hours:**

  * Summer: 9:00 - 7:00 pm

  * Winter: 9:00 – 6:00 pm

**Directions from Interstate 5 South**

  * Take the "Beach Cities" Exit and head west (toward the ocean) 

  * Follow this road (Pacific Coast Highway/Del Prado) into Dana Point. 

  * Turn left at Violet Lantern 

  * When you reach the stoplight at the corner of Violet Lantern and Del Prado,   
look left. Killer Dana is on the corner 

**Directions from Southbound PCH**

  * Follow PCH past Salt Creek into Dana Point. 

  * After you enter the "one-way" portion of PCH, continue two more blocks to Violet Lantern. 

  * Killer Dana is on the corner of Violet Lantern and PCH (Del Prado),   
just past the Post Office 

[View Larger Map  
](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=24621+Del+Prado,+Dana+Point,+CA+92629,+USA&ie=UTF8&z=17&iwloc=addr&om=1)[MAP TO KILLER DANA DANA POINT](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=24621+Del+Prado,+Dana+Point,+CA+92629,+USA&ie=UTF8&om=1&z=17&iwloc=addr)

##  **Killer Dana - San Clemente**  
128 Avenida Del Mar,  
San Clemente, CA 92672, USA  
949.492.2305 

**San Clemente Store Hours:**

  * Summer: 9:00 - 7:00 pm

  * Winter: 9:00 – 6:00 pm

**Directions from Interstate 5 South**

  * Take the "El Camino Real" Exit and head west (toward the ocean) 

  * Follow El Camino Real into San Clemente 

  * Turn left at Del Mar (stoplight) 

  * Killer Dana is on the right hand side in the first block at 128 Del Mar. 

**Directions from Southbound PCH**

  * Follow PCH South into San Clemente (the Coast Highway is called El Camino Real). 

  * Turn right on Del Mar. 

  * Killer Dana is on the right hand side in the first block at 128 Del Mar. 

[View Larger Map  
](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=128+Avenida+Del+Mar,+San+Clemente,+CA+92672,+USA&ie=UTF8&z=14&iwloc=addr&om=1&ll=33.435094,-117.610016&source=embed) [MAP TO KILLER DANA SAN CLEMENTE](http://maps.google.com/maps?q=128+Avenida+Del+Mar,+San+Clemente,+CA+92672,+USA&ie=UTF8&z=17&iwloc=addr&om=1)

**What are your store hours?**   

  * **Dana Point Store:**  
Summer: 9:00 - 7:00 pm  
Winter: 9:00 – 6:00 pm

  * **San Clemente Store:**  
Summer: 9:00 - 7:00 pm  
Winter: 9:00 – 6:00 pm

  * **The Warehouse:**  
Year round 9:00 – 5:00 pm, Monday – Friday, excluding holidays.   
_This can sometimes differ because our personnel may show up a little later or even earlier if the waves are good or bad._

## What is Killer Dana's Privacy Policy?

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. We will notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new policy on this website. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of our practices, as they may change in the future.

By visiting our site or sending us information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to continue operating this website, including the variety of information and services it contains. Similarly, we need you to provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted and, if you purchase anything, so that we can complete the transaction. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, you will not receive the information, product, and/or service you are requesting.

The personal information we collect includes your name and e-mail address. Other personal information that you submit is clearly labeled at the time you submit it. We use the information that we collect to provide our services, fulfill any purchase you may have made, send you our newsletter, contact you regarding new promotions, and to improve our site. We also use this information—directly, indirectly, and in combination with data we exchange with other parties—to introduce you to informational, service, and/or product offerings from us, our affiliated companies, partners, select unaffiliated companies, and/or assign (collectively, the “KILLERDANA.COM Companies”). We do this by transferring, licensing, and/or sharing your personal information with the KILLERDANA.COM Companies and hope you will be interested in their marketing materials and/or promotions. The KILLERDANA.COM Companies may subsequently transfer, and/or share your personal information. Once a third-party obtains your personal information, its subsequent use is controlled by the business practices of the third party, which is beyond our control. Note, however, that your payment information is used only for order processing purposes.

When submitting any information on our website you expressly authorize us to use your personal information as explained in this privacy policy, and you consent to receiving commercial email from us and all of the KILLERDANA.COM Companies. You can expect to receive newsletters, sweepstakes announcements, promotions, and other similar offers. Should you wish to discontinue receiving these e-mailings simply unsubscribe using the link in the email you receive.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to, the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and click stream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve it.

If you pay for anything on our site using a credit or debit card, we collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information includes your name, card number, and other necessary information, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you use to submit payment. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

Anything you send us, post on our site, or use with our service, such as blog postings or videos, or if others send us anything about your activities or postings, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We use this information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our customer agreements.

We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information by carefully limiting access to the database in which your personal information is stored. We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of wrongful conduct. We may also (and you authorize us to) disclose personal information about you to credit agencies, collection agencies, and/or merchant database agencies, as we deem necessary.

This website is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

To contact the owner and/or operator of this website, use the following contact information:

##  **Killer Dana - San Clemente**  
14350 Myford Road  
Irvine, CA 92606, USA  
949.428.2800 

_This privacy policy is effective as of June 30, 2009._
